Guida West Papers, 1946-2006
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VI. ORGANIZATION FILES
  - Monroe County (NY) Coalition for Welfare Justice, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Montclair Bureau of Public Welfare, 1959-64 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Montclair Fair Housing Committee (New Jersey), 1965-68, undated (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
  - Montclair Friends of Welfare Rights (FWRO) (Box 20)
    - General, 1969-72, undated (Box 20, Folder 13-15)
    - Notebooks, 1969, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Montclair Welfare Rights and Friends of Welfare Rights (Box 20)
    - General, 1970-72, undated (Box 20, Folder 17-18)
    - Binder, 1968-71 (Box 20, Folder 19-22)
    - Notebooks, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Funding proposals, 1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Interview and other notes, Nov 1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Montclair Mothers' Rights [WRO] (Box 21)
    - General, 1968-75, undated (Box 21, Folder 6-10)
    - Notebook, Aug-Nov 1971 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Montclair Parent Advisory Council (PAC) for Title I, Elementary and Secondary Education Act (ESEA) (Box 21)
    - General, 1968-71, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law conference, 11 Sep 1971 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Notebooks, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 14-16)
  - Morris County (NJ) Friends of Welfare Rights Organization, 1972-73 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Mount Vernon (NY) Self-Help Project, Inc., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Movement for Economic Justice/Jobs and Justice (Box 22)
    - General, 1973-80, undated (Box 22, Folder 2-8)
    - Just Economics newsletter, 1973-80 (Box 22, Folder 9-14)
  - National Anti-Hunger Coalition (NAHC) [Annie Smart], 1986-90, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - National Assembly for Social Policy and Development, 1964-75 (Box 23, Folder 2-4)
  - National Assembly of National Voluntary Health and Social Welfare Organizations, Inc., 1975-77 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1975-79 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Black Social Workers, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Social Workers (NASW), 1971-2000, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - National Campaign for Jobs and Income Support, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees (Box 23)
  - [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 23)
  - National Center for Children in Poverty (NCCP), 2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - National Clients Council, national and Essex County Chapter (NJ) [Ruby Grace], 1979-83, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - National Coalition on Women, Work, and Welfare Reform, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - National Committee on Employment of Youth, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - National Committee on Tithing in Investment, 1965, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - National Conference on Social Welfare, 1966-67 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A. (NCC) (Box 23)
    - General, 1958-2001 (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
    - Memo From the Washington Office, 1964-68 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Crusade Against Hunger, 1970-71 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Convocation of Conscience, 9-11 May 1973 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Luncheon with National Welfare Rights Organization, 5 Oct 1973 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - National Council of Negro Women (NCNW), 1996 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - National Council of Negro Women, Newark Section, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - National Council of Women's Organizations (Box 23)
  - [see also Council of Presidents] (Box 23)
    - General (Box 23)
      - 1999 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Domestic Priorities Task Force, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National Council on Women, Work, and Welfare, 1978-79 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National Farm Worker Ministry, 1971-73 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - National Jobs For All Coalition, 1996-2002, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National Network to Abolish Workfare, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Organization for Women (NOW) (Box 24)
    - General, 1976-2001, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Legal Defense and Education Fund (LDEF) (Box 24)
      - General, 1992, 1995-2003, undated (Box 24, Folder 8-11)
      - BOB Coalition (Building Opportunities Bonus), 1998-2001, undated (Box 24, Folder 12-13)
      - Conference, "To Promote the General Welfare: Ending Women's Poverty," 6-7 Mar 2000 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Leadership Summit "The Link Between Violence and Poverty," 28 Apr 1995 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Working Group on Domestic Violence and Welfare, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Task Force on Older Women, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - New Jersey, 1976-79 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York City Chapter, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - National Organizers Alliance, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - National Right To Work Committee, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - National Tenants Organization, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National Unemployed and Welfare Rights Organization (Box 25)
  - [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS] (Box 25)
  - National Urban League, 1972-75, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - National Welfare Monitoring and Advocacy Partnership, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - National Welfare Rights and Reform Union, 1988-91, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - National Welfare Rights Organization (NWRO) (Box 25)
    - General (Box 25)
      - 1967-71 (Box 25, Folder 9-17)
      - 1972-76, 1996, undated (Box 26, Folder 1-6)
    - Conventions and conferences (Box 26)
      - Action Conference, Chicago, 22-25 Aug 1968 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - National Conference, Pittsburgh, 22-26 Jul 1970 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Eastern Regional Conference, Waterbury, CT, 27-28 Nov 1970 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - National Conference, Providence, RI, 28 Jul-1 Aug 1971 (Box 26)
        - General (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Church-Related Friends of Welfare Rights meeting, 28-30 Jul (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - Notebook (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Eastern Regional Conference, New York Theological Seminary, 25 Feb 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Eastern Regional Survival Conference, Albany, NY, 9-11 Jun 1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - National Conference, Miami Beach, 5-9 Jul 1972 (Box 26)
        - Pre-conference materials (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - General (Box 26, Folder 16)
        - Coalition of Church-Related Friends of Welfare Rights Organizations meetings (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Notes (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Eastern Regional Conference, Baltimore, 11 Nov 1972 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - National Convention, Washington, DC, 11-15 Jul 1973 (Box 27)
        - Pre-convention materials (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - General (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - Notes (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - National Convention, St. Louis, MO, 11-14 Jul 1974 (Box 27)
        - Pre-convention materials (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - General (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Notes (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - National Convention, Los Angeles, CA, 17-19 Jul 1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - National Convention, Little Rock, AR, 4-6 Aug 1977 (Box 27)
        - General (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Notes (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Publications (Box 27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1969-72, undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - "Adequate Income Plan," 1968-71, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Membership materials (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - "New Food Stamp Bill of Rights," circa 1971 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Organizing kits (Box 27)
        - General, 1969-72 (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - Don't Buy Sears, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - Food rights, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 3)
        - Live on a Welfare Budget, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
        - School breakfast and lunch, 1970-72 (Box 28, Folder 5)
        - Utility rights, 1969-71 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - "Supplemental Security Income Program Advocates Manual," undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Title I, 1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - "Welfare Bill of Rights" and "Bill of Welfare Rights," undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - The Welfare Fighter, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - [see OVERSIZE MATERIALS for 1969-73] (Box 28)
      - "Your Rights in WIN-Talmadge," 1972 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - NWRO/Friends of NWRO (Box 28)
      - Notebook, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Notebook "Oct 1971," Oct-Dec 1971 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Notebook "Jan Feb 1972" (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Notes, 1972-75 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - National Welfare Rights Union (NWRU) (Box 28)
    - General: 1987-91, 1994-2000, undated (Box 28, Folder 16-19)
    - First Annual Convention, "Up and Out of Poverty," Detroit, 3-5 Sep 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1-1A)
  - National Woman's Party, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - National Women's Political Caucus (NWPC), 1973-77 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement, circa 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey Community Action Training Institute, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Council of Churches (Box 29)
    - General, 1965-70, undated (Box 29, Folder 6-13)
    - Task Force on Welfare, 1969-78, undated (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - New Jersey Displaced Homemakers Task Force, 1976-82, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - New Jersey Family Planning, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - New Jersey Friends of Welfare Rights (Box 29)
    - General, 1967-73, 1977, undated (Box 29, Folder 17-20)
    - Notebook, Aug-Sep 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey Friends of Welfare Rights/Welfare Rights Organization: notebook, Mar 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - New Jersey Welfare Rights Organization, 1969-83, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - New Jersey Interreligious Legislative Council (Box 30)
  - [see IMPACT] (Box 30)
  - New Jersey Network on Adolescent Pregnancy, Exchanges (ed. by Guida), 1980, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey Standard of Need Advisory Committee, 1989, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Welfare Council, 1967-74 (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
  - New Jersey Welfare Reform Working Group, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - New Priorities Movement, 1974-76, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - New York Urban Coalition, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Newark Clients Council, [Ruby Grace] 1978-79 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Newark and Essex County Legal Services Projects Joint Board of Trustees, 1970-71 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Newark Essex CORE, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Newark Welfare Rights Organization/Friends of Welfare Rights Organization, 1971-74 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Newark Youth Opportunity Center, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Occupational Emergency Center, Seattle [Bernardine Saulsberry], 1982, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Ohio Empowerment Coalition, Cincinnati, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Ohio Welfare Rights Organization/Ohio State Consumers Education Association [Margaret Willis & Colleen Shillington] (Box 30)
    - General, 1970, 1983-89 (Box 30, Folder 18-20)
    - Convention, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Annual Conference, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Older Women's League, 1978-80 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Paterson (NJ) Welfare Rights Organization/Friends of Welfare Rights Organization, 1972, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Philadelphia Citizens in Action, 1982-83 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Philadelphia Welfare Rights Organization (Box 31)
    - General, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - October/I Am on Welfare Program, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Poor People's Development Foundation, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Poverty/Rights Action Center, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Poverty Rights Office (Atlanta, GA), Poor People's Newsletter [EthelMaeMatthews], 1984-93 (Box 31, Folder 8-10)
  - Presbyterian Synod of New Jersey (Box 31)
  - [see United Presbyterian Church, Synod of New Jersey] (Box 31)
  - Presbytery of Newark (Box 31)
  - [see United Presbyterian Church, Synod of New Jersey] (Box 31)
  - Priests for Equality, 1977, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Project Equality of New Jersey, Inc., 1971, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Public Assistance Coalition, Wisconsin Council of Churches, 1970-73, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Public Interest Projects, Inc., 1996 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - RAP Inc., circa 1972 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Reform Organization on Welfare (ROWEL), 1973-74, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights, 1974-80, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Research for Education to Assist Children (REACH), 1969, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - RESULTS (Responsibility for Ending Starvation Using Legislation, Trimtabbing and Support"), 2000-01, undated (Box 31, Folder 19-20)
  - Rhode Island Fair, Welfare Rights Organization [Bertha Cavanagh], 1966-72, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Rochester Action for Welfare Rights [NY], 1972-73 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Rural Advancement Fund, 1971, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Rutgers University, 1969-73, 1980, undated (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
  - SANE, A Citizen's Organization for a Sane World, 1967-74, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Scholarship, Education and Defense Fund for Racial Equality (SEDFRE), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Social Agenda [Theresa Funicello] (Box 32)
  - [see also Downtown Welfare Advocate Center] (Box 32)
    - General, 1984-87, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Conference: "Social Policy and the Current Economic Crisis," 29 Nov 1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Social Concerns Action Network (SCAN) (Box 32)
    - General, 1972-78, undated (Box 32, Folder 7-12)
    - Conference on Poverty and the Federal Priorities, 12 May 1973 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Sojourners, 1978, 1999, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC), 1977-78 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Survivors, Inc. [Dottie Stevens], 1996-2005 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - United Black Workers, Ford Mahwah Assembly Plantation, Mahwah, NJ, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - United Church of Christ (Box 33)
    - General, 1966-2001, undated (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
    - United Church Board for Homeland Ministries (UCBHM) (Box 33)
      - General (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Deering Conference (Box 33)
        - National Economic Priorities, 17-22 Jul 1972 (Box 33)
          - General (Box 33, Folder 5)
          - Notebook (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - Planning for Social Change, 22-27 Jul 1973 (Box 33)
          - General (Box 33, Folder 7)
          - Notebook (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Deering Conference on National Health Insurance and Occupational Health, 15-19 Jul 1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Economic and Racial Justice Priority Team, 1976, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - "Economic Justice" newsletter, 1978-83 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Family Planning and Abortion Program, 1973-74 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Journal of Current Social Issues (Box 33)
        - 1968, 1973, 1974, 1976 spr and fall (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
        - 1976 winter, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Shalom Curriculum, "Shalom is Economic Justice," 1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Welfare Priority Team (Box 34)
      - [see also NWRO/FWRO] (Box 34)
        - General (Box 34)
          - 1970-Sep 1972 (Box 34, Folder 3-12)
          - Oct 1972-74 (Box 35, Folder 1-11)
        - Notes on NWRO/WPT directions, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 12)
        - Welfare Issues mailings, 1970-74, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - United Community Corporation, Newark, 1966, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - United Farm Workers, 1972-75, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - United Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A. (Box 36)
    - General, 1964-72, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Board of National Missions, Church and Race Memo, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Commission on Religion and Race, Religion and Race Memo, 1964-68 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
    - Committee on Church and Society (Box 36)
      - General, 1967-72 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Dialogue Program, 1964-65 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - "Still No Room at the Inn: a report on Public Assistance," by Nel Van Dijk and Guida West: notes, correspondence, drafts, 1966-67 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Commission on Religion and Race (SynCORR) (Box 36)
      - 1964-Apr 1967 (Box 36, Folder 10-17)
      - May 1967-68, undated (Box 37, Folder 1-5)
    - Presbytery of Newark, 1968-72, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - United Presbyterian Women, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - United Welfare Groups of Essex County (NJ), 1967-69 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - United Welfare Mothers of Hayes Homes, Newark, NJ, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - United Workers Organization, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Urban Coalition, 1969-74, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Urban Justice Center, 1999, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Urban League of Essex County (NJ), undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Urban Training Institute of Essex County (NJ), 1968-74, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Welfare Rights Organization, 1971, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Wages For Housework Campaign/International Wages for Housework Campaign, 1988-2002, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Washington Interreligious Staff Council (WISC), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Washington Research Project Action Council, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Washington Welfare Rights Organization (Seattle), 1969-71, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Made a Difference National Campaign (WMAD) (Box 37)
    - General, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 20-21)
    - National Day of Action, 14 Sep 2000 (Box 37)
      - General (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Lobbying (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Press conference (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - General, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 4-5)
    - Lobby trip, May 2001, Oct 2001 (Box 38, Folder 6-7)
    - General, 2002, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Lobby trip, Feb 2002, May 2002 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
    - Booklets, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Booklet drafts and correspondence, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Policy papers, 2000-01 (Box 38, Folder 13-14)
    - Policy papers source material, 1996, 2000-01, undated (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
    - Research: women's stories, 1994, 1999-2001, undated (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
    - Video, "Once Upon A Time & Welfare Made a Difference," 2003 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - [see also Series X. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS] (Box 39)
  - Welfare Reform Information Service Community (WRISC), 1973-75 (Box 39, Folder 6-11)
  - Welfare Reform Network (WRN) (Box 39)
    - General, 1993-2002, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Meetings, 1995-99 (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
    - Flyers, circular letters, and alerts, 1991-2005, undated (Box 40, Folder 1-4)
    - HandsNet online network, 1996-2000 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Mailing list, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - College Task Force, 1996-99, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - New York State "Jobs First" policy, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Federal Issues Committee, 2000-01 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Task Force on Women and Welfare (Box 40)
      - General, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - "Women's Response to 'So-Called' Welfare Reform," May-Jun 1997 (Box 40)
        - Drafts (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Authorization forms (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Newsletter, WRNews, 1991-2003 (Box 41, Folder 3-5)
  - Welfare Rights Advocacy Project, Hackensack, NJ, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Rights Initiative, Hunter College Center for the Study of Family Policy, 1995-2000 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - [see also SERIES VII. SPEECHES AND TESTIMONY] (Box 41)
  - Welfare Rights Organizations-Allegheny County (Pennsylvania) [WROAC] (Box 41)
    - General, 1969-79, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Friends group, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Newsletter The Welfare Righter (Box 41)
      - 1975-82 (Box 41, Folder 10-13)
      - 1983-85 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Welfare Rights Eastern Leadership Conference, Pittsburgh, 15-17 Aug 1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Rights Organizing Committee (Brooklyn, NY), 1989 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Warriors (Milwaukee, WI), 1987-97 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Wolfe County (KY) Rights and Information Center, 1972-73 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Women of Color Resource Center, 1994-95 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Women, Work, and Welfare (Minneapolis, MN), 1987-90, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Women's Action Alliance (WAA), 1978 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Women's Agenda of New Jersey, 1987-90, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Women's Campaign for Jobs and Economic Justice, 1982, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Women's Committee of One Hundred (WC100) (Box 42)
    - General, 1995-2010, undated (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - News clippings, 1995-2002 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Administrative (Box 42)
      - General (Box 42)
        - 1995 (Box 42, Folder 14-18)
        - 1996-97. n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1-12)
      - Financial, 1995-2002, undated (Box 43, Folder 13-17)
    - Correspondence (Box 43)
      - Steering Committee (Box 43)
        - 1995-Feb 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1-21)
        - Mar 1996-1999 (Box 45, Folder 1-22)
        - 2000-05, undated (Box 46, Folder 1-15)
      - General (Box 46)
        - Jan-Jun 1995 (Box 46, Folder 16-21)
        - Jul 1995-2001, undated (Box 47, Folder 1-7)
    - Events (Box 47)
      - Vigil for a Veto, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 8-10)
      - Lobbying Day, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 11-14)
      - Teach-Ins, 1996, undated (Box 47, Folder 15-18)
    - Meetings and conference calls (Box 47)
      - General, 1995-2001 (Box 47, Folder 19-21)
      - Other organizations (Box 47)
        - Sep-Oct 1995 (Box 47, Folder 22)
        - Dec 1995-96 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Notes (Box 48)
      - General, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Pad, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Notebook 1, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Notebook 2, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 5-10)
    - Publications, 1995-2002, undated (Box 48, Folder 11-14)
  - Women's Educational Equity Communications Network (WEECN), 1977-80, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Women's Equity Action League (WEAL), 1975-78, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF), 1971-75, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Women's Washington Representative, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONNAC), 1973 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Workers Action Movement (WAM), 1972, undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Young Women's Christian Association of Omaha, Displaced Homemakers Program, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-99, undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
- SERIES VII. SPEECHES AND TESTIMONY
  - "Racial Justice and Freedom," United Presbyterian Women, Metuchen, New Jersey, 24 Mar 1965 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Speech to United Presbyterian Women, Woodbridge, 16 Sep 1965 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Speech before Deacons re: Covenant of Open Occupancy, 5 Apr 1966 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - "With liberty and justice for all," Metuchen-Edison National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Freedom Fund Dinner, 23 Apr 1966 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - "The Twentieth Century Good Samaritan," Montclair, 6 Nov 1967 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Re: New Jersey Friends of Welfare Rights, Central Presbyterian Church, Montclair, 14 Jun 1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Welfare, Bridgewater League of Women Voters, 22 Sep 1970 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "The Welfare Crisis," Trenton, New Jersey, 16 Feb 1971 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "The Right To Live," Trenton Education Association Seminar for Teachers, 20 Apr 1971 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Reform, Unitarian-Universalist Fellowship of the Somerville Area, 18 Sep 1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - "The Social Protest of Poor Women: A Case Study of the National Welfare Rights Movement," Symposium on Women and Society, St. Michael's College, VT, 24 Mar 1979 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Statement for the Hearings on "The Coming Decade: American Women and Human Resources Policies and Programs," U.S. Senate Committee on Human Relations, 9 Apr 1979 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Unidentified speech, 1 Oct 1980 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - "Welfare Politics: Women in Welfare Reform Hearings, 1935-1980," Society for the Study of Social Problems, 30 Aug 1983 (Box 49, Folder 14-15)